const Questions = [
  {
    question:
      "I fly without wings, cry without eyes. Wherever I go, darkness follows me. What am I?",
    optionA: "A Cloud",
    optionB: "A Bat",
    optionC: "A Ghost",
    optionD: "A Moon",
    answer: "A Cloud",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I have cities but no houses, mountains but no trees, and water but no fish. What am I?",
    optionA: "A Map",
    optionB: "A Globe",
    optionC: "A Desert",
    optionD: "A Painting",
    answer: "A Map",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I'm not alive, but I can die. I'm not a plant, but I can grow. What am I?",
    optionA: "A Fire",
    optionB: "A River",
    optionC: "A Mountain",
    optionD: "A Shadow",
    answer: "A Fire",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I'm always in front of you, but you can never see me. What am I?",
    optionA: "The Future",
    optionB: "The Past",
    optionC: "A Mirror",
    optionD: "The Present",
    answer: "The Future",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I have keys but no locks. I have space but no room. You can enter, but you can't go inside. What am I?",
    optionA: "A Keyboard",
    optionB: "A Clock",
    optionC: "A Car",
    optionD: "A Piano",
    answer: "A Keyboard",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I'm a word of letters three, add two and fewer there will be. What am I?",
    optionA: "Few",
    optionB: "Four",
    optionC: "Five",
    optionD: "Free",
    answer: "Few",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I'm a number of digits three, subtract two and doubled I'll be. What am I?",
    optionA: "One",
    optionB: "Three",
    optionC: "Four",
    optionD: "Six",
    answer: "Four",
  },
  {
    "question": "I am a month of days thirty, add two and days I have plenty. What am I?",
    "optionA": "May",
    "optionB": "June",
    "optionC": "July",
    "optionD": "August",
    "answer": "June"
},
{
    "question": "I am a season of months three, subtract one and a warmer time you'll see. What am I?",
    "optionA": "Spring",
    "optionB": "Summer",
    "optionC": "Autumn",
    "optionD": "Winter",
    "answer": "Summer"
},
  {
    question:
      "I have a heart that doesn't beat. I can flow without water. What am I?",
    optionA: "A River",
    optionB: "A Clock",
    optionC: "A Tree",
    optionD: "A Road",
    answer: "A Clock",
  },
];

export default Questions;
